

Name
Dusan Odalovic

Website

www.odalovic.com

Address
Berlin 14199, Germany

Phone +49 176 6945 3205

Email

dodalovic@gmail.com

LinkedIn

LinkedIn

LinkedIn.com/in/dodalovic

Twitter

Twitter.com/odalinjo

PROFILE

Being a member of various development teams for over a decade helped me gain significant experience when dealing with businesses, technology and people.

Experience working on-site (Germany, UK, Poland) and remotely for clients worldwide.

Experience building scalable, cloud based, distributed software architectures.

Team leadership skills

java rest api kotlin spring kubernetes git docker kafka micro-services

EXPERIENCE	
2020 - Present	Senior software engineer - software architect
	Freelance
	Design and implementation of various backend oriented software solutions
2017 - 2020	Senior software engineer - software architect
	■ Market Logic Sofgware GmbH● Berlin / Germany
	Design and implementation of highly scalable, resilient and elastic document processing pipelines using asynchronous, micro-service architectures
2016 - 2017	Senior software engineer
	Avenso GmbHPerlin / Germany
	Designing scalable e-commerce solution based on existing microservices practices Leading role in designing and implementing set of stateless Rest APIs using Open-source tooling (Spring, Git, Mongo, Docker).
2010 - 2014	Senior software engineer
	⚠ Ascendant technology - Avnet services♠ Belgrade / Serbia
	IBM WebSphere Commerce based implementations for worldwide known clients. Open-source based solutions for UK & Ireland based clients
2010 - 2010	Software engineer
	Excelus DOOPelgrade / Serbia
	Development of portlet applications, as well as Automotive colaboration software development

LANGUAGES

- English fluent
- German intermediate
- Serbian native

EDUCATION

Faculty of organisational sciences - department for information systems and technologies

Belgrade, Serbia 2000 - 2009

